what's up you guys it's Matt here so
today I'm mixing Brands here you know I
got Nike right here I got Adidas up here
but really that does not matter what
does matter is the fact that we're
talking about xrp in the last video I
made I appreciate all of the different
views that we got and comments and stuff
for uh that video understandably uh so I
mean it's very very interesting to see
that
we may potentially know when they're
going to re-list xrp and also getting
the information from the the uh CEO
himself saying that you know the reason
why xrp was delisted it wasn't anything
really behind
um you know anything else where they
were just like oh we delisted it because
of lack of volume or anything it's
because of uh the fact that they wanted
to live by the rules
and living by the rules means that you
know the SEC says oh we're we're in a
battle with them so we're gonna do this
um but now that we're getting kind of
close to the end and people are
believing that xrp may end up winning
this lawsuit and all of that
um or at least coming out on top it
doesn't mean it necessarily has to be a
full win but anything that's really
related positively into or that's
positive towards xrp Cy I would say is
definitely a win
um for them in the end
but I wanted to talk about xrp here
today because some people don't believe
that the value is going to be as high as
you know people say it's going to be now
I know some of it can be absolutely it
seemed like it could be far-fetched it
seemed like it could be you know
completely out of this world
um and when it comes to a price but
anything could happen now obviously I'm
on the side where I'm like I'm more
skeptical than anything that it could
hit
20 000 uh dollars per coin or a hundred
thousand dollars per coin but I'm not
saying it's completely impossible I'm
saying that it would be highly unlikely
to have that happen I don't want to rule
anything out but I also don't want to
sit here and be like it's 100 gonna hit
a hundred thousand dollars a year or
sorry a hundred thousand dollars not a
hundred thousand dollars a year that
would be crazy if it found a way to drop
down and went up to 100 anyways it
doesn't matter but we're here to talk
about xrp in this video hopefully you
guys enjoy it make sure you guys hit the
like button hit the Subscribe button
hit that notification Bell for more
videos like this one also make sure you
guys check out some of the links down
below it does help out the channel and
if you guys want to follow me on Twitter
at Perry AK you can follow me over there
don't forget about some of the other
links that are in the description if you
guys want to check those links out feel
free to uh go ahead and check those out
um as well as my patreon I feel like my
patreon
um you know gets overlooked uh times we
do have some one-on-ones we just posted
a one-on-one um with a patreon member
and it was very beneficial to a lot of
people not only him
but me and other people can get some
strategies out of it as well now
um like I said I talked about xrp in the
video that I did today which obviously
for you I I did it the day before right
so
um we look at this video a re-listed xrp
for coinbase and this video got about 20
000 views the most views that I've
gotten in a while like I've had some
that had 10 that had that had had a 15
um but never or not in the level of 20
or above so this is fantastic to be able
to see that
and how many views it is getting so
thank you guys uh everybody that has
watched this video I appreciate it so
much
um but there was also some interesting
things uh that came with it where uh
people were just wondering like if I
truly believe that this is going to get
to a crazy price like not only worrying
about you know confirming where it's uh
you know confirming uh when it's getting
relisted or why it was uh delisted but
also just trying to get an understanding
of
whether it's going to get to a five
dollar ten dollar twenty dollar a
hundred dollar one hundred thousand
dollar price and honestly as you go up
the scale you you start to look at a
less likely
um less likelihood for it to get to
those uh levels
um you know the probability starts to uh
dwindle a little bit so uh I'm gonna get
into that let's go ahead and dive into
where xrp is right now so if we go over
to the chart
xrp is currently at about 51 and a half
or 52 cents it's really been around this
point for the whole entire time as you
know
um xrp was you know is in this or
ripples in this battle
um with the SEC to really uh kind of say
that they're not you know an
unregistered security
um
that they're not doing things illegally
here right
um that you're seeing and you saw a
price drop right you saw the price pull
back
um but not only pull back from that it
most likely pulled back from the overall
markets and how they were functioning
rather than you know just the lawsuit
because right now you're seeing a lot of
other cryptocurrencies getting hit and
being named
um as you know potential Securities and
some of those are really getting hit
hard like Adam or Solana or algoran
right getting hit very very hard
um and basically saying that everything
out there is a security besides Bitcoin
and that's what the SEC is saying so
you're seeing all of those kind of fall
back but xrp is sort of remaining the
same so xrp is showing that it has a ton
of strength seeing that at about 51 and
a half cents 52 cents
um showing a 27 billion dollar market
cap
um and this is what's phenomenal right
because we know that this can get back
up to a dollar right A dollar is not
really the level where people are like
all right well this is this is just
gonna get to a dollar and we're gonna
accept it there we know that it can go a
lot further than that
we know that xrp should be worth you
know tens of billion should be worth
hundreds of billions honestly and some
people believe that it should be worth
trillions or tens of trillions and some
people even hundreds of trillions now
I'm not really in where they are right
now I couldn't say that because the
markets they aren't even worth that much
and I always compare everything to the
uh thing that's leading the market which
is Bitcoin
and Bitcoin kind of will forever have
that that effect to where it's it's
definitely gonna be in the top five if
not stay at one the whole entire time
right I'm a big fan of ethereum and I
think ethereum can take over but with
how much people put into like what
Bitcoin is even though it's not the best
cryptocurrency out there right it's kind
of like um I don't know LeBron shoes
right you know that Michael Jordan shoes
are are fantastic but LeBron shoes still
cost like 250 dollars or you know 200 or
whatever right they cost the same amount
as what you would have with you know um
not not every single Jordan you know not
Jordan Ones or whatever right depending
on which ones they are Chicago's or
something
um it but what you're seeing is kind of
that comparison
um basically saying that this is this is
out here it's it's going to be up there
in the in the conversation but it has no
real reason to be up there not saying
that LeBron doesn't have a reason to be
up there but let's leave it away for
from a Sports Talk even though I brought
it there
um but yeah that's the way that I I see
it there so I know that there's a lot of
predictions for xrp to go up to three
dollars four dollars five dollars ten
dollars and I see those and I see those
as possibilities
um and some people there's a lot of
people actually that don't believe that
this is going to be the case at all that
xrp is just gonna dwindle down it's
going to decrease and nobody's gonna be
a fan of it anymore which is something I
don't believe I think it's going to be
worth way more than those people think
uh for the normal xrp holder the the
person that really loves this position
yeah of course you're going to have the
highest expectations possible
um but even your expectations sometimes
when you see it because you have your
expectations you have
um what reality is and then you have the
maximum amount that you can gain now the
maximum amount is you you probably look
at it and go well it has low probability
your expectation is probably a little
bit lower
um so I would say that a lot of your
expectations are going to be uh reached
if not
um exceeded the extra expectation so
um
xrp again if you guys want to look up
some predictions there's a lot of
predictions out there and look up the
reasons as to why you can see a hundred
thousand dollars per coin
um you know it makes me laugh because
it's it's definitely worth a hell of a
lot market cap wise but I can't say it's
absolutely impossible not gonna say that
so guys hit that like button hit that
subscribe button let me know what you
think about this um down below I'll be
trying to reach out to people as we're
you know stopping for different things
because we're going to be traveling
um all day but guys uh like I said hit
the like button hit the Subscribe button
hit that notification Bell for more
videos like this one I'm gonna get out
of here and I'll catch you in the next
one see ya